A Guide to the Papers of the Institute of Public Affairs, University of Virginia, 1927-1953
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Original Manuscripts-Round Table, Open Forum, Special Conference (Box 17-53)
  - Morning Addresses: "Financing Total War"
    - Panel Discussion: "Financing Total War," Rep. Thomas Eliot, Leader; "The ABC's of War Finance," Thomas C. Blaisdell, Jr.; "The Economic Consequences of War Finance," Richard M. Bissell, Jr. 1942 July 8 (Box 51)
  - Morning Addresses: "Inter-American Relations in War-Time"
    - Panel Discussion: "Inter American Relations in War-time," A. Curtis Wilgus, Leader; "Is Imperialism Dead in Latin America?," Samuel Flagg Bemis; "The Lasting Bases for Inter American Solidarity," Walter H. C. Laves; "Post War Planning--Why and How," Walter D. Head 1942 July 9 (Box 51)
  - Morning Addresses: "After the War: What Kind of an America?"
    - Panel Discussion: "After the War: What Kind of an America?," Hugh R. Pomeroy, Leader; "Goals for America," Stuart Chase; "Prospects of Post War Prosperity," William Wilson Cumberland 1942 July 10 (Box 51)
  - Morning Addresses: "The Organization of Power in the Post-War World"
    - Panel Discussion: "The Organization of Power in the Post War World," Brooks Emeny, Leader; "Design for a People's Peace," Frederick L. Schuman; "Conflicting Trends in Post War Planning," Percy E. Corbett 1942 July 11 (Box 51)
  - Afternoon Addresses: "The Geographical Pattern of the War"
    - Panel Discussion: "The Geographical Pattern of the War," Brooks Emeny, Leader; "Military Applications of German Geopolitics," H. W. Weigert; "The War in the Far East... ," Lt. William M. McGovern 1942 July 6 (Box 51)
  - Afternoon Addresses: "Science, Technology, and Modern War"
    - Panel Discussion: "Mobilization of Human Resources for the War Effort ;" "Manpower Problems and the War Effort," Brig. Gen. Frank McSherry; "Migration and the War Production Program," Robert K. Lamb 1942 July 7 (Box 51)
  - Afternoon Addresses: "The Emerging Pattern of Modern War"
    - Panel Discussion: "The Emerging Pattern of Modern War," Colonel R. Ernest Dupuy, Leader; "The Tactics of Modern War," Lt. Colonel Paul W. Thompson; "Air Power Comes of Age," Maj. Nathaniel F. Silsbee 1942 July 8 (Box 51)
  - Afternoon Addresses: "Strategies of Political and Moral Warfare"
    - Panel Discussion: "Strategies of Political and Moral Warfare," Brooks Emeny, Leader; "News as a Weapon," Matthew Gordon; "The Communications Front," Harold D. Lasswell; "The New Strategy," Brig. G. K. Bourne 1942 July 9 (Box 51)
  - Afternoon Addresses: "The Bases of the Future World Order"
    - Panel Discussion: "The Bases of the Future World Order," Brooks Emeny, Leader; "After Victory--What?," Mrs. Vera Micheles Dean; "Government by Force or Government by Law," Stringfellow Barr 1942 July 10 (Box 51)
  - Afternoon Addresses: "After the War: What Kind of a World Economy?"
    - Panel Discussion: "After the War--What Kind of a World Economy?," Theodore Kreps, Leader; "Labor and the New World Economy," Lewis L. Lorwin; "Agenda for Future World Trade," Arthur Upgren 1942 July 11 (Box 51)
  - Evening Addresses
    - "Map of the Future," Father John F. Cronin; "Religion for Such a Time as This," Rabbi Abraham Shusterman; "Religion Always on Trial," Rev. Beverly M. Boyd (empty) 1942 July 5 (Box 52)
    - "An Invitation to Public Thinking in War-time," Oron J. Hale; "Welcome on Behalf of the University," Dr. John Lloyd Newcomb; "Building in War for Peace," Hon. Dean G. Acheson 1942 July 6 (Box 52)
    - "Control of Strategic Materials in War and Peace," William Gandell Elliott; "The Far East: A Glance into the Future," Hon. Elbert D. Thomas 1942 July 7 (Box 52)
    - "America's Place in the Geography of War and Peace," Nicholas J. Spykman; "The Civilian Front in Wartime," Jonathan Daniels 1942 July 8 (Box 52)
    - "The Evolution of Pan Americanism," Dr. Don Luis Quintanilla 1942 July 9 (Box 52)
    - "Wartime Relations with Britain," Hon. Paul H. Appleby; "Inside Germany," Louis Lochner 1942 July 10 (Box 52)
    - "Congress and the War Effort," Hon. Alben W. Barkley; "New Zealand and the War in the Pacific," Hon. Walter Nash 1942 July 11 (Box 52)
  - Special Session: VA Council Administrative Women in Education (In conjunction w/ the Institute of Public Affairs)
    - "Some Phases of the Program in Cultural Relations," [Anora Marins] 1942 July 9 (Box 52)
    - "Towards a Governed World Community," Stringfellow Barr 1950 July 11 (Box 53)
  - Morning Addresses: "The Outlook for the Free World in Asia"
    - "Outlook for the Free World in Asia--India," Margaret Parton; "The Outlook for the Free World--Japan," Paul H. Clyde; "Outlook for the Free World in Asia: The Korean Viewpoint," Hon. Pyo Wook Han 1953 July 6 (Box 53)
  - Morning Addresses: "The Integration of Europe"
    - "Britain and European Integration," I. F. Porter; "Integration of Europe," Geoffrey W. Lewis; "American Leadership and the Integration of Europe," Georges Henri Martin; "Congress Looks at the Integration of Europe," Carl Marcy 1953 July 7 (Box 53)
  - Morning Addresses: "The United States in World Opinion"
    - "Foreign Economic Policy for the United States," Kenneth H. Campbell, Mrs. John G. Lee; "International Trade Issues," F. G. Singer 1953 July 8 (Box 53)
  - Morning Addresses: "World Problems: Population, Resources, and Technology"
    - Marquis Childs, Moderator; "The Soviet Image of the United States," M. J. Ruggles 1953 July 9 (Box 53)
  - Morning Addresses: "Community Organizations and Public Policies"
    - William Vogt; "Potential Plenty for the World's Future," Watson Davis; "World Problems--Population, Resources, and Technology," Norman G. Luker 1953 July 10 (Box 53)
  - Afternoon Addresses: "The Outlook in the Near and Middle East"
    - "The Outlook in the Near and Middle East," William Reitzel, Edwin M. Wright; [Address by William G. Hetherington] 1953 July 6 (Box 53)
  - Afternoon Addresses: "Free World and Soviet World: Is Co-existence Possible?"
    - "Free World and Soviet World," Is Co-existence Possible?," Stefan T. Possony; "The Soviet Concept of 'Co-existence'," John M. Maury, Jr.; "Plan V and Soviet Intentions," Demitri B. Shimkin 1953 July 7 (Box 53)
  - Afternoon Addresses: "The Economic Outlook in the United States"
    - "Economic Outlook in the United States," J. A. Livingston; "Economic Outlook in the United States--Midyear 1953," J. Dewey Daane; "Labor's View of the Economic Outlook in the United States," Boris Shishkin 1953 July 8 (Box 53)
  - Afternoon Addresses: "A Program for Truth About the United States"
    - "United States and World Opinion," Harry J. Krould 1953 July 9 (Box 53)
  - Afternoon Addresses: "National Security and Individual Freedom"
    - "National Security and Individual Freedom," Alan Barth, Leonard J. Ganse, Donald R. Richberg 1953 July 10 (Box 53)
  - Evening Addresses
    - "God in the City of Man," Rev. Thomas A. Carlin, O. S. F. S. 1953 July 5 (Box 53)
    - "American Responsibilities in the Free World," Senator A. Willis Robertson; "Britain's Responsibility in the Free World," Sir Roger Makins 1953 July 6 (Box 53)
    - "Latin American Background and Outlook," Dr. Alberto Lleras; "[Outlook for a Free Asia]," Walter H. Judd 1953 July 7 (Box 53)
    - "Technology and National Research Policy," M. A. Tuve; "United States Information Service--Its Meaning to the United States Taxpayer," Coulter D. Huyler, Jr. 1953 July 9 (Box 53)
    - Address by Hon. Alexander Wiley (R., Wis), Chairman, Senate Foreign Relations Committee; "The Responsibility of the Press for Leadership in a Democracy," Hamilton Owens 1953 July 10 (Box 53)
- Series III: Correspondance and Miscellaneous Records (Box 54-145)
  - Budget [1927-1930] (Box 54)
  - Gasoline Tax [1927] (Box 54)
  - Founding of Institute 1927 (Box 54)
  - Institute--Miscellaneous 1927-1951 (Box 54)
  - Miscellaneous "A--D" 1927, 3 folders (Box 54)
  - Photographs of Speakers 1927 (Box 54)
  - Printed Materials 1927-1953 (Box 54)
  - Prohibition--Correspondence 1927 (Box 54)
  - Reports 1927-1942, 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Reports--Copies 1927-1942 (Box 54)
  - Round Table Discussions--Growth of Taxation and Expenditures 1927 (Box 55)
  - Statistics--Former Sessions 1927-1942 (Box 55)
  - Biographies of Speakers 1928 (Box 55)
  - W. Jefferson Davis 1928 (Box 55)
  - Delegates 1928 (Box 55)
  - Form Letters, Reports, Cards 1928-1941 (Box 55)
  - Dr. Henry S. Haskell--Carnegie Endowment for International Peace [1928] (Box 56)
  - Dr. A. R. Hatton [1928] (Box 56)
  - Dr. John H. Latané 1928 (Box 56)
  - Letters Regarding Manuscripts 1928 (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous"A--N" 1928, 14 folders (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous "P-W" 1928, 6 folders (Box 57)
  - Speakers--Accepted 1928 (Box 57)
  - Speakers--Asked 1928 (Box 57)
  - Photographs 1928 (Box 57)
  - Published Material 1928 (Box 57)
  - Report and Budget [1928-1929], 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Announcements 1929 (Box 58)
  - Biographical Sketches 1929 (Box 58)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace 1929 (Box 58)
  - Comments on Sessions 1929 (Box 58)
  - Contributions 1929 (Box 58)
  - Copies of Biographical Sketches 1929 (Box 58)
  - Delegates 1929 (Box 58)
  - Delegate List-checked letters (Maphis) 1929 (Box 58)
  - Delegate List-checked letters (Gov) 1929 (Box 58)
  - Endowment Campaign 1929 (Box 58)
  - Inter-American Institute-University of Mexico 1929 (Box 58)
  - Miscellaneous "A-Z" 1929, 12 folders (Box 59)
  - Dr. Raymond Moley 1929 (Box 59)
  - Dr. Thomas H. Reed [1929] (Box 59)
  - Report and Budget [1929] (Box 59)
  - Report of the Round Table on the "Task of the Country Church" [1929] (Box 59)
  - Hon. C. Bascom Slemp [1929-1930] (Box 59)
  - Speakers--Asked 1929 (Box 59)
  - Photographs 1929 (Box 59)
  - Biographical Sketches 1930 (Box 60)
  - Contributions 1930 (Box 60)
  - Delegates 1930 (Box 60)
  - Dr. Clarence A. Dykstra [1930] (Box 60)
  - Expense Accounts [1930] (Box 60)
  - Dr. C. J. Galpin--Department of Agriculture [1930] (Box 60)
  - Governors--Regard Delegates 1930 (Box 61)
  - Dr. C. H. Haring [1930] (Box 61)
  - Maj. Hodges [1930] (Box 61)
  - Dean Charles G. Maphis 1930 (Box 61)
  - Dr. Henry W. McLaughlin [1930] (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous "A--Z" 1930, 22 folders (Box 62)
  - Arthur J. Morris [1930] (Box 62)
  - Original Biographies 1930 (Box 62)
  - Photographs 1930 (Box 62)
  - Positions 1930 (Box 62)
  - Reception--Monticello 1930 (Box 62)
  - Dr. Thomas H. Reed [1930] (Box 62)
  - Regrets 1930 (Box 62)
  - Report and Budget [1930-1931] (Box 63)
  - Round Table Leaders 1930 (Box 63)
  - Speakers--Asked 1930 (Box 63)
  - Adult Education [1931] (Box 63)
  - Biographical Sketches 1931 (Box 63)
  - Board of Advisors [1931] (Box 63)
  - Dr. Louis Brownlow [1931] (Box 63)
  - Gov. Harry Flood Byrd [1931] (Box 63)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace [1931] (Box 63)
  - David R. Coker [1931] (Box 64)
  - Comments on 1930 Session [1931] (Box 64)
  - Comments on 1931 Session [1931] (Box 64)
  - Contributions [1931] (Box 64)
  - Delegates 1931 (Box 64)
  - Duplicate vouchers or pay-rolls [1931] (Box 64)
  - Editorials [1931] (Box 64)
  - Expense Accounts [1931] (Box 64)
  - Governor--Regarding Delegates 1931 (Box 65)
  - Dr. Frederick C. Hicks [1931] (Box 65)
  - Maj. LeRoy Hodges [1931] (Box 65)
  - Herman G. James [1931] (Box 65)
  - Mailing Lists 1931 (Box 65)
  - Dr. Henry W. McLaughlin [1931] (Box 65)
  - Spencer Miller [1931] (Box 65)
  - Miscellaneous "A--Z" 1931, 24 folders (Box 66)
  - Dr. Raymond Moley 1931 (Box 66)
  - Monroe Celebration-Correspondence with Diplomats 1931 (Box 66)
  - Monroe Celebration-Correspondence with Persons Invited 1931 (Box 67)
  - Monroe Memorial Centennial Commission 1931 (Box 67)
  - Photographs 1931 (Box 67)
  - Positions 1931 (Box 67)
  - Presentation of Byrd Portraits 1931 (Box 67)
  - Dean Roscoe Pound, "Law Enforcement" 1931 (Box 67)
  - Dr. Thomas H. Reed 1931 (Box 68)
  - Regrets 1931 (Box 68)
  - Reports of Secretaries for Various Round Tables [1931] (Box 68)
  - Round Table Leaders 1931 (Box 68)
  - C. Bascom Slemp [1931] (Box 68)
  - Speakers--Asked 1931 (Box 68)
  - Speakers--Suggested 1931 (Box 68)
  - Dr. Rob Tucker [1931] (Box 68)
  - Biographical Sketches 1932 (Box 69)
  - Louis Brownlow, Leader, Round Table on Regionalism [1932] (Box 69)
  - Carnegie Foundation for International Peace [1932] (Box 69)
  - Comments on Session 1932 (Box 69)
  - Contributions and Correspondence with Foundations, etc., in regard to aid [1932] (Box 69)
  - Delegates--Miscellaneous 1932 (Box 69)
  - Dr. H. W. Dodds [1932] (Box 69)
  - Duplicate Vouchers [1932] (Box 69)
  - Expense Accounts [1932] (Box 69)
  - Dr. C. H. Haring [1932] (Box 70)
  - Dr. Henry W. McLaughlen [1932] (Box 70)
  - Members 1932 (Box 70)
  - Rev. Minor C. Miller 1932 (Box 70)
  - Spencer Miller, Jr. 1932 (Box 70)
  - Miscellaneous "A" 1932 (Box 70)
  - Miscellaneous "A-W" 1932, 17 folders (Box 71)
  - Gilbert H. Montague 1932 (Box 71)
  - Dr. Marcus Nadler [1932] (Box 71)
  - John Lloyd Newcomb [1932] (Box 71)
  - Personal 1932 (Box 71)
  - Photographs 1932 (Box 71)
  - Receipts [1932] (Box 71)
  - Dr. Thomas H. Reed 1932 (Box 72)
  - Regrets 1932 (Box 72)
  - Rotary Clubs [1932-1935] (Box 72)
  - Speakers--Asked 1932 (Box 72)
  - Special Conferences [1932] (Box 72)
  - "Thank You" Letters 1932 (Box 72)
  - Dr. Robert H. Tucker 1932 (Box 72)
  - Biographical Sketches 1933 (Box 73)
  - Budget 1933 (Box 73)
  - Campaign Funds 1933 (Box 73)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace [1933] (Box 73)
  - Grover Clark [1933] (Box 73)
  - Contributions [1933] (Box 73)
  - Delegates 1933 (Box 73)
  - Duplicate Vouchers [1933] (Box 73)
  - Dr. C. H. Haring [1933] (Box 73)
  - Letters of Appreciation 1933 (Box 73)
  - Dr. Robert McElroy 1933 (Box 74)
  - Dr. Henry H. McLaughlin [1933] (Box 74)
  - Mailing Lists 1933 (Box 74)
  - Rev. Minor C. Miller [1933] (Box 74)
  - Spencer Miller [1933] (Box 74)
  - Miscellaneous "A--T" 1933, 20 folders (Box 74)
  - Felix Morley [1933] (Box 75)
  - Ray Newton [1933] (Box 75)
  - Photographs 1933 (Box 75)
  - Positions 1933 (Box 75)
  - Receipts [1933] (Box 75)
  - Reception at Monticello 1933 (Box 75)
  - Regrets 1933 (Box 75)
  - Report and Project [1933] (Box 75)
  - Reports of Secretaries of Round Tables [1933] (Box 75)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration 1933 (Box 75)
  - Speakers--Asked 1933 (Box 75)
  - Dr. George W. Spicer [1933] (Box 75)
  - Dr. H. Parker Willis [1933] (Box 75)
  - Alumni Association 1934 (Box 76)
  - Biographies 1934 (Box 76)
  - Board of Advisors 1934 (Box 76)
  - Budget 1934 (Box 76)
  - Senator Harry Flood Byrd 1934 (Box 76)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace [1934] (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Senator Harry Flood Byrd 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Dr. J. A. C. Chandler 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Zachary Taylor Dinner 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Dr. Douglas S. Freeman 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Dr. Francis P. Gaines 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Stuart G. Gibboney 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Senator Carter Glass 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Hugh Gordon Miller 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Hon. R. Walton Moore 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--R. F. Nelson 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--President F. D. Roosevelt 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Dr. Charles J. Smith 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Hon. Claude A. Swanson, Secretary of the Navy 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Jacquelin P. Taylor 1934 (Box 76)
  - Zachary Taylor Celebration--Joseph A. Werne 1934 (Box 76)
  - Contributing Memberships 1934 (Box 76)
  - Charles Hall Davis 1934 (Box 76)
  - Hon. John W. Davis 1934 (Box 76)
  - Daughters of the British Empire 1934 (Box 76)
  - Duplicate Vouchers [1934] (Box 76)
  - Expense Accounts [1934] (Box 76)
  - Form Letters 1934 (Box 76)
  - Report on Institute for Dr. Gee 1934 (Box 76)
  - Colonel LeRoy Hodges 1934 (Box 76)
  - John W. Davis Luncheon--Given by Morris L. Strauss 1934 (Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous "A-W" 1934, 22 folders (Box 77)
  - Hon. R. Walton Moore, Assistant Secretary of State 1934 (Box 77)
  - Motion Picture Research Council 1934 (Box 77)
  - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs, Inc. [1934] (Box 77)
  - Photographs 1934 (Box 77)
  - Gov. George C. Peery 1934 (Box 77)
  - President John Lloyd Newcomb [1934] (Box 78)
  - President of the United States, Franklin D. Roosevelt 1934 (Box 78)
  - Receipts [1934] (Box 78)
  - Regulations for Occupants of Dormitories [1934] (Box 78)
  - Round Table-"Adult Education" [1934] (Box 78)
  - Round Table: "An Evaluation of the N. R. A."
    - Dr. Carmen Haider, Leader [1934] (Box 78)
    - David Cushman Coyle [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. Leon Henderson [1934] (Box 78)
    - Robert W. Johnson [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dexter Keezer [1934] (Box 78)
    - Isabel Leighton [1934] (Box 78)
    - Spencer Miller, Jr. [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. Gustave Peck [1934] (Box 78)
    - Program of Round Table [1934] (Box 78)
    - Donald Richberg [1934] (Box 78)
    - F. J. Schlink [1934] (Box 78)
  - Round Table: "County Government and State Planning"
    - W. F. Day [1934] (Box 78)
    - Howard P. Jones [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. John W. Manning [1934] (Box 78)
    - Hon. C. H. Morrisett [1934] (Box 78)
    - Program for Round Table [1934] (Box 78)
    - Hon. Lemuel F. Smith [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. George W. Spicer [1934] (Box 78)
    - Tipton R. Snavely [1934] (Box 78)
    - Charles P. Taft, II [1934] (Box 78)
  - Round Table: "Currents of Conflict in the Far East"
    - Grover Clark [1934] (Box 78)
    - Ben Dorfman [1934] (Box 78)
    - Doubleday, Doran, and Company [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. Harley F. McNair [1934] (Box 78)
    - Zhi Meng (Chih Meng) [1934] (Box 78)
    - C. K. Moser [1934] (Box 78)
    - Program [1934] (Box 78)
    - Prof. Masamichi Royama [1934] (Box 78)
    - Mrs. F. Louis Slade [1934] (Box 78)
    - Miles Vaughn [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. Quincy Wright [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. N. Gist Gee [1934] (Box 78)
  - Round Table: "Dictatorship and Democracy"
    - Harry E. Barnes [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. Francis W. Coker [1934] (Box 78)
    - Laurence Dennis [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. Benjamino de Ritis [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. John Dickinson [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. Karl F. Geiser [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. Sidney Hook [1934] (Box 78)
    - Alvin Johnson [1934] (Box 78)
    - Oakley Johnson [1934] (Box 78)
    - Algernon Lee [1934] (Box 78)
    - Julian S. Mason [1934] (Box 78)
    - Program for Round Table [1934] (Box 78)
    - Dr. Henry R. Spencer [1934] (Box 78)
  - Round Table: "The Function of the Church in Modern Life"
    - Dr. Will W. Alexander [1934] (Box 79)
    - Rev. Cameron Parker Hall [1934] (Box 79)
    - Rev. Stanley High [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. John McDowell [1934] (Box 79)
    - Program for the Round Table [1934] (Box 79)
  - Round Table: "The Good Neighbor Policy with Latin America"
    - Dr. Ricardo J. Alfaro [1934] (Box 79)
    - Hon. William R. Castle [1934] (Box 79)
    - Carlos G. Davila [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. W. E. Dunn [1934] (Box 79)
    - Orestes Ferrara [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Samuel Guy Inman [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Warren Kelchner [1934] (Box 79)
    - Fred Lavis [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Dana G. Munro [1934] (Box 79)
    - Benjamin Muse [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Robert L. O'Brien [1934] (Box 79)
    - Program for Round Table [1934] (Box 79)
    - Paul Vanorden Shaw [1934] (Box 79)
    - G. Butler Sherwell [1934] (Box 79)
    - Doris Stevens [1934] (Box 79)
    - Francis White [1934] (Box 79)
  - Round Table: "Home Ownership and the Country Church"
    - Dr. Harold E. Fey [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. G. W. Forster [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Arthur Wentworh Hewitt [1934] (Box 79)
    - Mrs. E. B. Ireland [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Henry W. McLaughlin [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. L. R. Manny [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Clarence Poe [1934] (Box 79)
    - Program for Round Table [1934] (Box 79)
    - Rev. John C. Siler [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Carl C. Taylor [1934] (Box 79)
    - R. W. Vanderberry [1934] (Box 79)
  - Round Table: "The Interpretation and Evaluation of Recent Trends in Education"
    - Wilford M. Aiken [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Ralph R. Bridgman [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Robert C. Brooks [1934] (Box 79)
    - Albert Coates [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Sidney B. Hall [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Joseph K. Hart [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Edgar W. Knight [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Joy E. Morgan [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. William T. Polk [1934] (Box 79)
    - Jacques Ozanne [1934] (Box 79)
    - Program for Round Table [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. Floyd W. Reeves [1934] (Box 79)
    - Dr. George A. Works [1934] (Box 79)
    - A. D. Zanzig [1934] (Box 79)
    - George B. Zehmer [1934] (Box 79)
  - Round Table: "Management Versus Regulation in Government"
    - A. J. Hettinger, Jr., Leader [1934] (Box 79)
    - Stephen M. DeBrul [1934] (Box 79)
    - Joseph B. Eastman [1934] (Box 79)
    - Mordecai Ezekiel [1934] (Box 79)
    - George Harrison Huston [1934] (Box 79)
    - Frank R. McNinch [1934] (Box 79)
    - Program [1934] (Box 79)
    - Colonel M. C. Rorty [1934] (Box 79)
    - Lawrence H. Seltzer [1934] (Box 79)
    - Wallace Thompson [1934] (Box 79)
    - P. M. Tuttle [1934] (Box 79)
  - Round Table: "Money: A Challenge to World Statesmanship"
    - Willard E. Atkins [1934] (Box 80)
    - Beatrice Comeau [1934] (Box 80)
    - W. W. Cumberland [1934] (Box 80)
    - George W. Edwards [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. Herbert F. Frasser [1934] (Box 80)
    - Lewis Galantiere [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. Charles O. Hardy [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. F. Cyril James [1934] (Box 80)
    - Bernard Kilgore [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. E. A. Kincaid [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. Wallace McClure [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. Leo Pasvolsky [1934] (Box 80)
    - Program for Round Table [1934] (Box 80)
    - Louis Rasminsky [1934] (Box 80)
    - Prof. James G. Smith [1934] (Box 80)
    - Robert B. Warren [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. Ralph J. Watkins [1934] (Box 80)
    - Ray B. Westerfield [1934] (Box 80)
  - Round Table: "Protestants, Catholics, and Jews"
    - Newton D. Baker [1934] (Box 80)
    - Rabbi Edward N. Calisch [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. Everett R. Clinchy [1934] (Box 80)
    - Walter J. Canaty [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. Abraham Cronbach [1934] (Box 80)
    - Prof. Horace M. Kallen [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. John Lapp [1934] (Box 80)
    - Rev. Thomas E. Mitchell [1934] (Box 80)
    - Rabbi David De Sola Pool [1934] (Box 80)
    - Program of Round Table [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. John E. Ross [1934] (Box 80)
    - Rev. Claris Edwin Silcox [1934] (Box 80)
    - Prof. James V. Thompson [1934] (Box 80)
  - Round Table: "Religious Education"
    - Edna M. Baxter [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. George C. Bellingrath [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. Z. B. Edworthy [1934] (Box 80)
    - Dr. George Walter Fiske [1934] (Box 80)
    - C. A. Hauser [1934] (Box 80)
    - Florence M. Hostetter [1934] (Box 80)
    - Frances C. McLeeter [1934] (Box 80)
    - Rev. Minor C. Miller [1934] (Box 80)
    - Rev. Edward B. Pailey [1934] (Box 80)
    - Program of the Round Table [1934] (Box 80)
    - Report [1934] (Box 80)
  - Rotary Club of Staunton [1934] (Box 80)
  - Rotary Club of Roanoke [1934] (Box 80)
  - Rotary Club of Winchester [1934] (Box 80)
  - Rotary Club of Charlottesville [1934] (Box 80)
  - Rotary International [1934] (Box 80)
  - Round Table: "Scholarships for Church" [1934]
  - Round Table: "Special Conference by General Federation of Women's Clubs"
    - Mrs. Fred M. Alexander [1934] (Box 80)
    - Mrs. Hampton Fleming [1934] (Box 80)
    - Mrs. Fred L. Pigeon [1934] (Box 80)